this is just a fun nostalgic little
story way back when say like three years
ago when they made the new software and
game development category
um there I stayed in the Science and
Tech category because I was
streaming things about Science and Tech
not software
development and I had at least four or
five people come at me I mean come at me
they came at me in my chat people who
did
even I didn't even know them you know
the whole read the room thing no
completely they're like they had somehow
they had somehow joined the cult of like
missionaries who were advocating for
this new awesome group and if you
weren't in the group you sucked and I'm
not even kidding they came into my
chat this is this is a cautionary tale
okay they came into my community without
establishing any kind trust or Report
with anybody in my community and they
started going off in my chat off
topic about why I wasn't in the
sophomore and game dep category and like
oh my God you're back in this old
category oh this other category is so
much better you should really be there
and they just nobody asked their
opinion nobody asked their opinion
nobody asked their opinion nobody cared
and they came in everybody else is we're
like all scratching our head like why
who are these people and and so I
started making memes about
it I started making memes about it in
fact I still have it somewhere I have I
have the Gil foil and Ganesha you know
guys know Gil foil and Ganesh from from
Silicon
Valley and so I making me and I and then
it became like a civil freaking War oh
my God people started cancelling me why
are you doing all this stuff and I was
like I was just having fun I was like
these people came into my chat and
they're like telling me that I suck
because I'm not changing my category I'm
like who are you number
one hi YouTube
and so so I I wish I could find the meme
I don't know if I still have it I wonder
where it is I have to go find a picture
but I had a picture of gilfoil and
Ganesha if you know them that's this one
is the Ops person right you know Gil
foil is like the you know the sigma
developer he's like 10x you know 100x
developer building Anton in you know his
his garage you know he's Ultra capable
he can do anything that Gil oil I mean
that Ganesh can do um dises can do dises
is like a programmer you know and a Java
and there's this whole thing they had
this whole back and forth all time it's
really really great I love it and and so
I the meme that I did is I put on Desh I
put software and game Deb in like puppy
comic sand spawn with pink letters and I
put it above his head and above gilfoil
I put Science and Tech where all the
hackers are and you know the people that
are doing real [__] and it pissed people
off man oh my God oh my
God people were so mad at me for that
they were so mad how dare you said like
you're literally called game
de compared to Science and Technology we
have we have like phds and microbiology
and astronomers and people like that
streaming to Science and Tech and these
you know script kitdiy
from the software in game devb are
giving me crap because I am you know and
then they started getting mad at me as
like looking down my nose at them and
I'm like you just came into my
house and told me that I sucked and now
you're telling me that I'm looking B my
nose at you it was so
funny it was so funny to this day I'm
still laughing about it and I I just
can't I can't I cannot believe how
broken
the
technology and programming content on
the Internet is it's so totally broken
it's it's all algorithm and stuff like
that and you know Finding good content
is so hard it's just so hard and so you
know don't get mad get busy make content
you know spend your Saturday and Friday
nights making videos and reminiscing
about the good old days back when we had
fights about what twitch category to
stream to